Dominic Micheli



UI / UX Designer

www.dominicmicheli.com dvm.micheli@gmail.com (386) 299-3589

About Me

As a UI / UX Designer with a diverse background in graphic design, entrepreneurship, sales, and leadership, in multiple industries, I have a unique and broad purview into business success with a holistic lens. Working in these diverse environments in multiple roles has allowed me to assess and address the microcosm needs within the macrocosm landscape, while delivering elegant and robust experiences to our user base.

Experience

Founder and Lead Designer - DVM Designs

2011 - Current, Remote

DVM Designs is a boutique Design Agecny

- 400 + Completed Projects: print, logo design, UI Design, web design, branding, marketing materials, packaging.
- Built a sustainable freelance business: by providing professional service, effective communication and timely design deliverables.

Co-Founder and Brand Manager - Nektor Sunscreen

2016 - 2019, San Diego, CA

Nektor Sunscreen is an all natural & sustainable suncare brand in the surf and lifestyle space.

- \$263,000 in revenue in year 1: by developing E-Commerce platform and product placement into 150 + retail brick and mortar accounts.
- **Developed and Managed Brand:** through extensive user research and testing, product development and testing, competitor evaluations, logo design, branding, product packaging, website design and brand ambassador program.

Sales Manager - Full Circle Nutrition

2011 - 2016, Daytona Beach, FL

Full Circle Nutrition is a community health and wellness center.

- 102% Increase in revenue from \$1.2M \$2.4M: within 3 years by implementing sales and growth strategies.
- 10,000 + lives impacted: by creating a team and customer success first methodogy, by boosting interest in company offerings with special events and marketing intiatives such as free community group exercise classes, sponsored 5k races, weight-loss challenges, hosting charity events and workplace fitness challneges.

Education

B.A. Graphic Design - Daytona State College

2008 - 2011, Daytona Beach, FL

UI / UX Immersion - CareerFoundry

2020, Online

Tools

Adobe XD

Figma

Sketch

Photoshop

InVision & Craft

Flinto

Atom

Skills

UI Design

UX Design

Wireframing

Prototyping

User Flows

UX Research

User Interviews

User Testing

Design Thinking

Branding

Leadership & Management

Team Building

Project Planning

HTML, CSS, JAVA Basics